[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Is anybody winning that argument?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "anybody", "winning", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I don't think it's an argument that either one of these men can win because it's so dependent, almost entirely dependent on events beyond their control.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "argument", "that", "either", "one", "of", "these", "men", "can", "win", "because", "it", "'s", "so", "dependent", ",", "almost", "entirely", "dependent", "on", "events", "beyond", "their", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "I mean isn't that the reality, a stain on all your houses?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "n't", "that", "the", "reality", ",", "a", "stain", "on", "all", "your", "houses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "You know, the -- the problem is that everybody is a little bit right.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "--", "the", "problem", "is", "that", "everybody", "is", "a", "little", "bit", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "How many men of that age shower with boys of 13, 14?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "men", "of", "that", "age", "shower", "with", "boys", "of", "13", ",", "14", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "But what is your feeling about what has gone wrong with America incorporated?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "your", "feeling", "about", "what", "has", "gone", "wrong", "with", "America", "incorporated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't think we're really facing up to our problems.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "'re", "really", "facing", "up", "to", "our", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Would you vote for him?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "vote", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "You know, I would -- I still lean towards him, because I know nothing about -- I still don't feel I know anything about Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "--", "I", "still", "lean", "towards", "him", ",", "because", "I", "know", "nothing", "about", "--", "I", "still", "do", "n't", "feel", "I", "know", "anything", "about", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "And I never, ever thought that I would.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "never", ",", "ever", "thought", "that", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "And the main reason for that would be what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "main", "reason", "for", "that", "would", "be", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I just feel -- you know, he had a good first two years.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "feel", "--", "you", "know", ",", "he", "had", "a", "good", "first", "two", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "He's how old now?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "how", "old", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Zach is now 28.", "answer_tokens": ["Zach", "is", "now", "28", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "When did you first realize this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "first", "realize", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "You know, I would say around the ages -- you know, I don't really remember, maybe 10 to 12, he has a phenomenal memory.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "say", "around", "the", "ages", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "remember", ",", "maybe", "10", "to", "12", ",", "he", "has", "a", "phenomenal", "memory", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Is it like the character of Dustin Hoffman?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "like", "the", "character", "of", "Dustin", "Hoffman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes, I mean it is a little bit like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "is", "a", "little", "bit", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dustin Hoffman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What was the intention of this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "intention", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "The intention was not to rediscover my son.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "intention", "was", "not", "to", "rediscover", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What did you learn about fatherhood that maybe surprised you when you went on this trip?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "fatherhood", "that", "maybe", "surprised", "you", "when", "you", "went", "on", "this", "trip", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, I think it's about acceptance.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "about", "acceptance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Or does he just judge you purely on your personal qualities as a father?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "he", "just", "judge", "you", "purely", "on", "your", "personal", "qualities", "as", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "He has -- he has some concept.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "has", "--", "he", "has", "some", "concept", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Yes, since the last time I saw you, I thought you would never invite me back.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "since", "the", "last", "time", "I", "saw", "you", ",", "I", "thought", "you", "would", "never", "invite", "me", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Chateau le Tour?", "question_tokens": ["Chateau", "le", "Tour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Yes, it's a Chateau le Tour.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "Chateau", "le", "Tour", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Are they called the Fallonettes?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "called", "the", "Fallonettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "They are not.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "How do you jump this rock star shot?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "jump", "this", "rock", "star", "shot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Thanks, god.", "answer_tokens": ["Thanks", ",", "god", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 397, "question": "The new look?", "question_tokens": ["The", "new", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "The new look -- I'm just losing --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "new", "look", "--", "I", "'m", "just", "losing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Are you not taken so seriously as a rock star?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "not", "taken", "so", "seriously", "as", "a", "rock", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I just have this compilation of all this music and maybe it is going in my ahead a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "have", "this", "compilation", "of", "all", "this", "music", "and", "maybe", "it", "is", "going", "in", "my", "ahead", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Bruce Springsteen, I mean incredibly, you got him to cover Willis Smith's hit, right?", "question_tokens": ["Bruce", "Springsteen", ",", "I", "mean", "incredibly", ",", "you", "got", "him", "to", "cover", "Willis", "Smith", "'s", "hit", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "\"Whip My Hair.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Whip", "My", "Hair", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce Springsteen", "Willis Smith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "-- The Boss?", "question_tokens": ["--", "The", "Boss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "The Boss.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Boss", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Is he serious?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "And it's like, if you think about it, when would he -- when would he ever see Bruce dressed like he was 30 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "like", ",", "if", "you", "think", "about", "it", ",", "when", "would", "he", "--", "when", "would", "he", "ever", "see", "Bruce", "dressed", "like", "he", "was", "30", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Listen, it's a brilliant album.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "brilliant", "album", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "How did you persuade him to do that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "persuade", "him", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "It was one of these weird things.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "one", "of", "these", "weird", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 545, "question": "It's just the joy of competition, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "the", "joy", "of", "competition", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Or did you deliberately lose to her to try and get the --", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "did", "you", "deliberately", "lose", "to", "her", "to", "try", "and", "get", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "-- with the president?", "question_tokens": ["--", "with", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "No, because we did everything inside the White House.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "we", "did", "everything", "inside", "the", "White", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "CC", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Do you think you're enhancing the reputation of your nation and its great leader by doing a sack race the East Room, a potato race?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "enhancing", "the", "reputation", "of", "your", "nation", "and", "its", "great", "leader", "by", "doing", "a", "sack", "race", "the", "East", "Room", ",", "a", "potato", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Well, the goal of this is to get children to get fit and workout and do --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "goal", "of", "this", "is", "to", "get", "children", "to", "get", "fit", "and", "workout", "and", "do", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Room"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "And you had a private meeting with the president before this -- the slow jam?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "had", "a", "private", "meeting", "with", "the", "president", "before", "this", "--", "the", "slow", "jam", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 578, "question": "How does that go?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Well, the -- it's -- by protocol, they want you to meet the president alone, because you invited him, so you -- so I'm -- I have to be there in -- no -- no stage manager, no assistants, no Fallonettes, no one is allowed to --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "--", "it", "'s", "--", "by", "protocol", ",", "they", "want", "you", "to", "meet", "the", "president", "alone", ",", "because", "you", "invited", "him", ",", "so", "you", "--", "so", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "have", "to", "be", "there", "in", "--", "no", "--", "no", "stage", "manager", ",", "no", "assistants", ",", "no", "Fallonettes", ",", "no", "one", "is", "allowed", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 718, "question": "-- who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["--", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "-- why would I impersonate someone with three minutes left --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "why", "would", "I", "impersonate", "someone", "with", "three", "minutes", "left", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "I want to show God my act?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "show", "God", "my", "act", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "Don't be so American literal about this.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "be", "so", "American", "literal", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Can you get more index cards laid out?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "get", "more", "index", "cards", "laid", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "So this \"Call Me Maybe,\" even my kids back in England, who wouldn't necessarily know who you are, now know you're the guy from the \"Call Me Maybe\" clip, because two million hits on YouTube.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "this", "``", "Call", "Me", "Maybe", ",", "''", "even", "my", "kids", "back", "in", "England", ",", "who", "would", "n't", "necessarily", "know", "who", "you", "are", ",", "now", "know", "you", "'re", "the", "guy", "from", "the", "``", "Call", "Me", "Maybe", "''", "clip", ",", "because", "two", "million", "hits", "on", "YouTube", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "Would you turn down the \"Tonight Show\" if you were offered it?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "turn", "down", "the", "``", "Tonight", "Show", "''", "if", "you", "were", "offered", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "No, I wouldn't turn it down.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "turn", "it", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "Is it -- is it the Holy Grail?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "the", "Holy", "Grail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120613pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Hasn't it always been the Holy Grail as a -- as a talk show host in America?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "n't", "it", "always", "been", "the", "Holy", "Grail", "as", "a", "--", "as", "a", "talk", "show", "host", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "I think it's the story around it, but it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "the", "story", "around", "it", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]